<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>Braindump Junkyard</title>
	<link href="http://iljakuklic.github.io/posts.xml" rel="self" />
	<link href="http://iljakuklic.github.io" />

	<entry>
		<title>A stupid trick to marginally increase your command line productivity</title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://iljakuklic.github.io/posts/2015-11-26-stupid-command-line-trick.html"/>
		<updated>2015-11-26T00:00:00+0000</updated>
		<content type="html">
			<p>Navigating directories in the command line (and elsewhere) can be annoying at times. Number of tools exist to migitate the annoyance. For example, the <code class="lang-bash">cd</code> command remembers the previous path before actually changing the directory. Then, <code class="lang-bash">cd -</code> can be used to quickly go back to the previous location and efficiently alternate two most recent positions <code class="lang-bash">cd</code>-ed into.</p>

			<p><a href="http:/iljakuklic.github.io/posts/2015-11-26-stupid-command-line-trick.html">Read on</a>.</p>
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<title>Non-regular types in Java</title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://iljakuklic.github.io/posts/2015-05-14-nonregular-types-java.html"/>
		<updated>2015-05-14T00:00:00+0000</updated>
		<content type="html">
			<p>Ironically, the first real post on this blog is about a programming language I hardly ever use. I could not think of technical reason why Java could not support non-regular types and polymorphic recursion as these two features are usually enabled by the type erasure property. But is it really the case? Googling did not seem to reveal the answer so I decided to find out myself. The short answer is yes, you can have non-regular data types in Java. The long answer is the rest of this post.</p>

			<p><a href="http:/iljakuklic.github.io/posts/2015-05-14-nonregular-types-java.html">Read on</a>.</p>
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<title>Hello, Internets!</title>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://iljakuklic.github.io/posts/2015-04-01-hello-internets.html"/>
		<updated>2015-04-01T00:00:00+0000</updated>
		<content type="html">
			<p>This place is going to be a storage space for <a href="/about.html">my</a> ideas and thoughts. Unorganized and messy. Sometimes looking more like it was written by a random bad pun generator rather than a human being. Containing a weird mixture of small hidden gems (I hope there will be some eventually) and a heap of toxic and otherwise dangerous or at least utterly useless material (pretty sure about this).</p>
<p>Welcome to <em>Braindump Junkyard</em>.</p>

			<p><a href="http:/iljakuklic.github.io/posts/2015-04-01-hello-internets.html">Read on</a>.</p>
		</content>
	</entry>

</feed>
